https://2strokebuzz.com/about/2strokebuzz-privacy-policy

Skip to content
2strokebuzz.com operates the https://2strokebuzz.com website, which provides the SERVICE.
This page is used to inform website visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information if anyone decided to use our Service, the 2strokebuzz.com website.
If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation with this policy. The Personal Information that we collect are used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.
Information Collection and Use
For a better experience while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information, including but not limited to your name, phone number, and postal address. The information that we collect can be used by 2strokebuzz.com to contact or identify you.
Log Data
We want to inform you that whenever you visit our Service, we collect information that your browser sends to us that is called Log Data. This Log Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser version, pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, and other statistics.
Cookies
Cookies are files with small amount of data that is commonly used an anonymous unique identifier. These are sent to your browser from the website that you visit and are stored on your computer’s hard drive.
Our website uses these “cookies” to collection information and to improve our Service. You have the option to either accept or refuse these cookies, and know when a cookie is being sent to your computer. If you choose to refuse our cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of our Service.
For more general information on cookies, please read “What Are Cookies”.
Service Providers
We may employ third-party companies and individuals due to the following reasons:
To facilitate our Service;To provide the Service on our behalf;To perform Service-related services; orTo assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.
To date (September 2020) we have never sold or shared your information with other providers, aside from what is publically visible to browsers of the site. It’s possible in the future that such third parties could be given access to your personal information. The reason is to perform the tasks assigned to them on our behalf. However, they would be obligated not to disclose or use the information for any other purpose.
Security
We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, thus we use reasonably practicable and currently-accepted means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure and reliable, and thus we cannot guarantee your data’s absolute security.
Links to Other Sites
Our Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over, and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.
Children’s Privacy
Our Services do not address anyone under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal identifiable information from children under 13. In the case we discover that a child under 13 has provided us with personal information, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information, please contact us so that we will be able to do necessary actions.
Changes to This Privacy Policy
We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, we advise you to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately, after they are posted on this page.
Contact Us
If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us.
Decades of Content! Decades of Content!
Scooter Kids!
Diamo (and Italjet)
Garelli
Genuine (LML/PGO)
Gilera
Honda
Kinetic (and Italjet)
Vespa Vid. Veds.
Scooter News
Concepts/Innovation
Green Scooters
100mpg?
Search for:
Search
